Guide to the Vera L. Connolly Papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
Vera L. Connolly Papers
1907-1960
[Bulk dates: 1916-1956].
Connolly, Vera L., 1888-1964.
12 linear feet ( 27 document boxes, one oversize box)
Columbia University. Rare Book and Manuscript Library, New York, NY.
4078648
This collection documents the career of Vera Connolly, journalist, editor, and fiction author, through her drafts, notes, and correspondence. Connolly's articles, published in popular magazines such as Good Housekeeping, Colliers, and Woman's Day, ranged in topic from financial advice for married women to juvenile delinquency, prison reform, sweatshops, and poor living conditions on Indian reservations.
Biographical Note
Vera Leona Connolly was a journalist and editor for many of America's popular magazines, particularly woman's journals such as Good Housekeeping, The Woman's Home Companion, and Woman's Day, from the 1920s through the 1950s. Describing herself as a "crusading journalist--a stirrer-upper," Connolly wrote articles that publicized and criticized social problems in the United States, including juvenile delinquency, lax adoption regulations, ineffective narcotics law, sweatshops, and the poor living conditions on Indian reservations. She encouraged her readers get involved by writing to government officials and volunteering time, and some of her articles sparked investigations and court cases that lead to significant changes. Connolly also wrote extensively about marriage and family throughout her career, but supported the rights of unmarried women and unwed mothers as well.
Connolly was born in 1888 at a military post in Benicia, California. Her father, an Army captain, traveled widely throughout Europe and Southeast Asia and often brought his wife and two children, Vera and Donald, with him. For several years he was stationed on the Round Valley Reservation in California, and Connolly later said that the poverty and malnourishment she witnessed there led to her decision to help disadvantaged groups.
The family eventually settled in Angel Island, San Francisco, where Connolly began writing stories and worked on her high school's newspaper. She went on to study English at the University of California for two years, but left after her father died of a bullet wound sustained in battle. Finding herself financially responsible for her handicapped mother, the 18-year-old Connolly moved to New York City to work as a reporter for the New York Sun. By 1913 she was Associate Editor of Delineator Magazine, and from 1917 to 1918 she ran a department at the Christian Herald called "Adventures in Neighboring," which featured upbeat articles about community improvement in rural areas. Connolly became Associate Editor of World Outlook in 1919 and worked for several months at McCalls.
In 1920, with enough editing experience to know what the magazines were looking for, Connolly began writing articles on contract. Over the next two decades she would publish hundreds of pieces in popular magazines, particularly Good Housekeeping. During the 1920's and early 1930s, Connelly focused on family and juvenile courts, youth crime waves, and prison conditions. She visited over 200 jails to see prison life in person. Connolly also visited sweatshops and wrote "Paid in Sweat" to expose the working conditions in the clothing industry.
In 1928, William Bigelow, editor of Good Housekeeping, sent Connolly on a year-long investigation of Indian reservations in the Western states. She returned to write four articles that accused the Indian Bureau of severe neglect, particularly at government boarding schools. The series, which relied heavily on Connolly's observations and the words of the Indians themselves, elicited hundreds of responses from shocked readers, as well as letters of denial and protest from Commissioner of Indian Affairs Charles Burke. The protests led to a Senate investigation and the appointment of a million dollars to feed Indian children, and may also have forced Burke's resignation. Connolly's third article, "The End of the Road," was entered into the Congressional Record. She considered the series one of her greatest accomplishments.
Connolly continued to write articles on social problems throughout the 1930s and 1940s. She attacked narcotics laws in "The Dope Menace" and warned potential adoptive parents in "Bargain Counter Babies." In 1933, her article "the Light in the Mountains" on rural mountain schools resulted in the Perpetual Vera Connolly Scholarship. She was especially interested in juvenile delinquency and discipline, and "Get the Children Out of the Jails," published in Woman's Home Companion in 1945, led to legislation restricting the jailing of children in several states. A later article, "No Straps, No Paddles," was reprinted by the U.S. Department of State, translated into many languages, and distributed in fifty-five countries to provide an example of how troubled and traumatized children could be treated without physical punishment. Connolly was also disturbed by rising divorce rates and wrote extensively about solutions to marital problems.
During the earlier years of her career, Connolly also published short stories and serials in fiction magazines such as Black Cat and The Cavalier. Her work ranged from animal adventure stories to mysteries, but many of her pieces were similar in theme to her articles. Her cautionary tale "The Incident" was based on interviews with two teenage runaways, and stories such as "The Spell on the Rice" focused on women trapped in unhappy marriages. She also experimented with poetry, musicals, and radio scripts, submitted movie concepts to film studios, and published a young adult novel entitled Judy Grant, Editor. Fiction remained a secondary interest, however, and Connolly eventually dropped most other projects to focus on journalism.
In 1937 Connolly became one of the founders and the Associate Editor of Woman's Day, where she was responsible for the column "Just Between Neighbors" and a tear-out section for children called "Children's Day." Two years later, she was asked to found and edit a woman's page for The Christian Science Monitor. She moved to Boston and created "Today's Woman," an eight-column page that covered the achievements of woman around the world and delved into issues especially important to women.
Connolly returned to New York and to contract writing in 1942, and wrote for Collier's and Women's Home Companion. She also published in Nation's Business, This Week, and the Saturday Evening Post, and served again as Associate Editor of The Delineator from 1945 to 1950. Her articles continued to have a powerful impact; "The Man who Refused to Die," published in Redbook in 1952, told the story of veteran Sam Harrison's determination to have a job despite having lost all but two fingers. The article was celebrated by disabled veterans, some of whom formed "Sam Harrison Clubs" to help others in similar situations. CBS made the story into a half-hour radio drama, and the U.S. Committee on Employment of the Physically Handicapped reprinted and distributed the article to hospitals and rehabilitation centers.
By the mid-1950s, woman's magazines had begun to turn away crusading pieces in favor of entertainment articles, and Connolly found it increasingly difficult to publish her work. She stopped publishing in 1955. Connolly died in New York in 1964.
Scope and Content
The bulk of the collection relates to Connolly's work as a contract and freelance writer and contains correspondence with editors and agents, extensive research notes, and many drafts of her published and unpublished work. It also includes clippings and scrapbooks of published articles, reviews and reactions to her work, and a small amount of biographical information
Arrangement
This collection is arranged in four series.
Series I: Correspondence, 1917-1960
Subseries I.1: Alphabetical, 1928-1955
Subseries I.2: Chronological, 1917-1960
Series II: Nonfiction, 1916-1956
Subseries II.1: Titled Drafts and Research Notes, 1929-1956
Subseries II.2: Untitled Drafts and Research Notes, 1916-1954
Subseries II.3: Article Clippings, 1917-1954
Series III: Fiction, 1907-1952
Subseries III.1: Titled Drafts, 1912-1952
Subseries III. 2: Untitled Drafts and Notes, 1907-1954
Series IV: General, 1917-1952.
Subjects
Connolly, Vera L., 1888-1964.; United States--Social conditions.; Adoption.; Divorce.; Social problems.; Marriage.; Journalism.; Juvenile delinquency.; Juvenile probation.; Prisons.; Reformatories.; Runaways.; Rural schools.; Indians of North America.; Women and journalism.; Articles.; Reprints.; Women journalists.; Women social reformers.; Christian Science monitor.; Good housekeeping.; Redbook.; Saturday evening post.; Woman's day.; Woman's home companion.
Access Restrictions
This collection has no rstrictions.
This collection is located off-site. You will need to request this material at least twenty-four (24) hours in advance to use the collection in the Rare Book and Manuscript Library reading room.
Acquisition
1965 M-65 Estate of Vera Connolly Gift
Gift of the estate of Vera Connolly, 1965.
Finding aid in repository; folder level control.
- Series I: Correspondence, 1917-1960.
  Most of the letters that make up this series are between Connolly and the agents and editors of magazines. Connolly presents concepts for unwritten articles, receives feedback and suggestions on drafts, and negotiates the direction of the articles. There are also some responses from readers.
  - Subseries I.1 Alphabetical, 1928-1955
    This subseries is arranged by personal or institution name and includes correspondence with W.F. Bigelow, editor of Good Housekeeping, and publishers at McGraw Hill and Dodd, Mead, and Co., among others.
    - Author's League, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Bigelow, W. F.--editor, Good Housekeeping, 1929-1931 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Brandt & Brandt--Agents, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Bye, George, 1936-1942 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - CBS, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Collier's, 1943-1949 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Congressional Christian News Bureau, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Cotton, Thomas L.--Correspondence, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Delineator, 1928-1932 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Dodd, Mead, and Company, 1937-1950 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Good Housekeeping, 1928-1933 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Harrison, Sam, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Hoover, J. Edgar, 1936, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - McCall's Magazine, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - McGraw-Hill, 1950-1955 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Montgomery, George, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Ober, Harold, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Reader's Digest, 1954-1955 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Redbook Magazine, 1947-1951 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Saturday Evening Post, 1951-1952 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - State of California Youth Authority, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Tallulah Falls School, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - This Week, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Today's Woman, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - William Morris Agency, 1950-1951 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Subseries I.2: Chronological, 1917-1960
    This small subseries contains a file of correspondence related to fiction submissions and several separate runs of general correspondence with editors, agents, and occasionally readers and friends.
    - Fiction Submissions, 1921-1924 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Editors and Agents, 1930-1960, (2 Folders) (Box 2, Folder 11-12)
    - General Correspondence, 1917-1955 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - General Correspondence, 1919-1947, (7 Folders) (Box 3, Folder 1-7)
    - General Correspondence, 1948-1958, (3 Folders) (Box 4, Folder 1-3)
    - General Correspondence, Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Series II: Nonfiction, 1916-1956
  Most of Connolly's nonfiction files contain a combination of research notes and drafts of magazine articles. Lists of article concepts and notes from interviews are also present, and some files, such as those relating to the American Indian series, contain extensive correspondence. Clippings of the finished article are sometimes available, but most drafts are undated and few include information on where the article was eventually published. A partial list of articles is included in her resume (see Series IV), but Connolly's published articles can be most easily found by searching magazine indexes, particularly those for Good Housekeeping, The Christian Science Monitor, Colliers, Redbook, Reader's Digest, The Delineator, The Saturday Evening Post, and Woman's Day.
  - Subseries II.1: Titled Drafts and Research Notes, 1929-1956
    Titled drafts of published and unpublished works have been arranged alphabetically. Many files also contain associated research notes.
    - American Indian Series, 1929
      - "The Cry of a Broken People," 1929 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - "Can a Crushed Race be Saved?" undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - "The End of a Long, Long Trail," 1929 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - "Is it the End of the Road?" 1929 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Reactions--Clippings and Correspondence, 1929, (2 Folders) (Box 4, Folder 9-10)
      - Reactions--Clippings and Correspondence, 1929, (2 Folders) (Box 5, Folder 1-6)
      - Reactions--Clippings and Correspondence, 1929, (2 Folders) (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
    - "Charm Helps Win the War"--USO Charm Schools, circa 1943 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - "Children for Hire--Cheap," 1943 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - "Clinics that Explain the Marriage Law," undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - "Communities that Saved Themselves"--radio concept, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - "County Pork Barrel"--County Jails, 1945-1946
      - Drafts, undated (Box 6, Folder 7-10)
      - Notebooks, undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, 1945-1946 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - "Delinquent Kids are Rejected Kids"--Youth House, circa 1946, (2 Folders) (Box 7, Folder 2-3)
    - "Do Our Kids Matter?"--Concept for Book on Juvenile Delinquency, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - "Does Your Child Have a Guardian?" undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - "Don't Stay Away from the Child Guidance Clinic," 1953 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - "Doped Americans"--Sleeping Pills, 1942-1945, (3 Folders) (Box 7, Folder 7-9)
    - "Doped Americans"--Sleeping Pills, 1942-1945, (3 Folders) (Box 8, Folder 1-3)
    - "Down into Ol' Virginny for an Afternoon with Lord and Lady Astor," undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - "Eat to Grow Famous"--Celebrity Diets, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - "Finding a Pot of Gold--In a Cotton Dress"--Florida Fashions, Inc., undated (contains photographs) (Box 8, Folder 6-9)
    - "Firehouse 13 Leads the Way"--Social Halls, undated, (2 foldres) (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
    - "Five Million Young Detectives,"--Know Your Money Campaign, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - "George Mason: The Man Who Wouldn't Sign," undated, (3 Folders) (Box 9, Folder 4-6)
    - "Get the Children Out of the Jails," 1944-1946, (3 Folders) (Box 9, Folder 7-9)
    - "Get the Children Out of the Jails," 1944-1946, (5 Folders) (Box 10, Folder 1-5)
    - "Going to School with Mom and Dad"--City College Courses, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - "The Happiest Husband and Wife Team in Showbusiness"--Peter Lind Hayes and Mary Healy, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - "Has Your Husband Made a Will?" undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - "How to Borrow Money," circa 1949 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - "How Not to Buy a House," 1948, (2 Folders) (Box 10, Folder 10-11)
    - "I was an Adopted Child," by Josephine Antoine as told to Connolly, 1946-1947 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - "A Job for a Lady"--Policewomen, 1943-1944, (3 Folders) (Box 11, Folder 2-4)
    - "Kangaroo Courts," 1945, (2 Folders) (Box 11, Folder 5-6)
    - "The Long, Long Arm of ISS," 1952 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - "Little Children on the Crime Road"--Juvenile Delinquency, 1936 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - "Man all Boats"--Fire Hazards on Ships, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - "The Man Who Refused to Die"--Sam Harrison (Box 12)
      - Notes and Drafts, 1950-1951 (Box 12, Folder 1-7)
      - Interview, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Radio Script, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - "No Place Like Home,"-Boarding Homes for Children, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - "Old Maids and Glad of It!"--Single Women, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - "Paid in Sweat"--Sweatshops, 1933 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - "A Park Vacation for a Song"--artwork, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - "Robbing the Veteran," 1956 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - "Speak up for Courtesy," 1950 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - "Starting on a Shoestring"--Small Businesses, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - "Taping Your Bumper May Save Your Life"--Auto Accidents, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - "They Cleaned Up a Blackboard Jungle"--Patrick Henry Junior High School, NYC, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - "The Tiffany of Doll Makers"--Madame Alexander, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - "Vera Connolly Drops in for a Chat"--radio news program, 1940 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - "When Parents Disagree,"--Progressive Education, 1944-1945, (3 Folders) (Box 13, Folder 12-14)
    - "Where Harbor Whistles Blow," undated, (2 Folders) (Box 13, Folder 15-16)
    - "Will You be a Foster Mother?" 1944 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - "You-And Your District Judges," circa 1949, (2 Folders) (Box 14, Folder 2-3)
    - "You Can't Get Away From it All"--Western Influence, circa 1938 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - "You Don't Have to Punish Kids"--Youth House, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Subseries II.2: Untitled Drafts and Research Notes, 1916-1954
    Files containing untitled drafts or research notes only have been arranged by subject, though these may relate to one or more of the titled drafts.
    - Article Ideas
      - Notes, circa 1949 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Notes and Partial Drafts, undated, (4 Folders) (Box 14, Folder 7-10)
      - Article Summaries, undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - Notes and Partial Drafts, undated, (4 Folders) (Box 15, Folder 1-4)
    - Canada--Articles inspired by Trips, 1916-1918 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Child Detention Center--Buffalo County New York--notebooks, undated, (3 Folders) (Box 15, Folder 6-8)
    - Child Labor, circa 1943 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Children in Jail, 1942-1954, (2 Folders) (Box 16, Folder 2-3)
    - Christian Science, undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Coal Mining, 1923 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Counterfeiting, 1944 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - County Jails, 1943-1946 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Delinquency, 1943-1952, (4 Folders) (Box 16, Folder 8-11)
    - Divorce, 1949-1951 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Dog Shows, undated (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Erie Canal, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Erie Canal, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 17, Folder 2-3)
    - Espionage, 1945 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Federal Civil Defense Administration Training School, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Foster Parents' Plan for War Children (organization), 1948 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Framington Reformatory, 1948, (2 Folders) (Box 17, Folder 7-8)
    - Health Clinic--Notebook, undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Home Engineering Plan, undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Investment, undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Hoover, J. Edgar, 1942-1944 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Jails
      - Research Articles, circa 1939 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Regulations, 1944 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Photographs of Lynchburg City Jail, Virginia, and Anderson County Jail, Tennessee, 1946-1947 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Migrant Workers, 1945 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - National Traveler's Aid Association--Runaway Case Studies, 1943-1952 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Sandy Hook Pilots, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Savings, 1949-1950 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Trefflich, Henry--Animal Dealer--Interview, 1948 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Trieste Refugee Camps --photographs, undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Series II.3: Article Clippings, 1917-1954
    Scrapbooks and clippings of published articles can be found in this subseries. They are organized alphabetically by publication title.
    - Multiple Magazines, 1922-1951, (3 Folders) (Box 18, Folder 11-13)
    - Christian Science Monitor --To Change the Subject (editorial), 1941 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Good Housekeeping
      - Articles, 1926-1929, (3 Folders) (Box 19, Folder 1-2)
      - Poster Ads, 1927-1928 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Reader's Digest, 1944-1954 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - General Articles, 1938 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - "Children's Day" Section, 1925-1939, (2 Folders) (Box 19, Folder 6-7)
    - Zest: The National Savings Newspaper, 1924-1925 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - "Just Between Neighbors", 1938-1939, (3 scrapbooks) (Box 20)
    - Oversize
      - Multiple Magazines, 1926-1944 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Christian Herald --"Adventures in Neighboring," 1917-1918, (2 Folders) (Box 21, Folder 2-3)
      - Collier's, 1943-1946 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - The Delineator, 1938-1930, (2 Folders) (Box 21, Folder 5-6)
      - Woman's Day --Scrapbook, 1938-1939 (Box 21)
- Series III: Fiction, 1907-1952
  This series is composed primarily of drafts and occasional printed copies of Connolly's short stories, poems, radio and television concepts, and her novel Judy Grant: Editor. Like her nonfiction articles, few of Connolly's fiction drafts are dated, although most were probably written before 1920. Files occasionally contain research notes, correspondence with publishers and editors, or clippings of published works and their associated illustrations.
  - Subseries III.1: Titled Drafts, 1912-1952
    This subseries contains drafts and notes of titled works, arranged alphabetically.
    - "Apartment to Let," undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - "At Go-Down #5," 1912 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - "Big Ben," undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - "Big Bob's Little Mary," undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - "Blitz Receives a Cablegram," undated (Box 22, Folder 5-6)
    - "The Book-ends," undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - "The Cotton Charmer"--Musical, undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - "The Fighting Spirit"--Radio Concept, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - "The Girl Next Door," undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - "He Belong Me," undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - "The Hill Girl," undated (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - "Hissie's Crowd," undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - "In from the Banks," undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - "The Incident," undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - "Juan of the Hills," undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Judy Grant: Editor, circa 1941, (4 Folders) (Box 23, Folder 5-8)
    - Judy Grant: Editor, 1940, (2 Folders) (Box 24, Folder 1-3)
    - "Last Bus to Paradise," undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - "Lest We Forget," undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - "The Little Cross Woman," undated (Hawke) (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - "Low Bridge," undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - "The Lone Trail," undated (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - "Mahogany Nutmegs," undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - "Moon Girl," undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - "The Mystery of the Chinese Cove," undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - "Ole's Senerio," 1942, (2 Folders) (Box 25, Folder 1-2)
    - "The Prairie Devil," 1947 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - "The Quest," undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - "S.S. Ladybird," undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - "Shy Elizabeth," undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - "The Snare," undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - "The Spell on the Rice," undated, (3 Folders) (Box 25, Folder 8-10)
    - "Squirrel-Oaks," undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - "Tenderfoot Nan," 1913 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - "Touch-off," undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - "The Turtle," undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - "Under White Men's Blankets," undated (Hawke) (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - "Women Are Crazy," undated (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Subseries III.2: Untitled Drafts and Notes, 1907-circa 1952
    Story concepts, notes, and untitled drafts can be found in this subseries.
    - Children's Stories, undated (Box 26, Folder 7)